Hey, I mean, I am going to do something ambitious for the next five minutes.
I will tell you what I think your adoption bottleneck on Cantonese.
I will propose a wedge to break it and show you the working code I will around that thesis.
I might be talking past you on a few things, but please, please grill me at the end.
I will find out tonight, then next month.
Here's the thing, Cantonese wins regulated multi-party tokenization.
Pricycy by design atomic interoperability that model that fits how easy to shine actually work.
Hydra X wins because you are the regulated rails for Southeast Asia.
But the thing is also rails alone don't drive adoption.
The bottleneck between we have rail and issue a ship's product on them is the workflow layer above.
That's where you can grow fastest and that's the layer I would.
Three assumptions I'm making name upfront so you can block them.
One institution won a tenant's surface.
You provide not their own boot.
Two, your roadmap once a white label, workflow plain, not bespoke per deal,
engineering three, Cantonese selective disclosure.
Cantonese selective disclosure is what made that plan defensible.
Again, a generic SaaS competitor tell me which breaks and the rest of this presentation
reshape your answer.
Instead of just pitching, I build the thing.
The repo is Hydra X at app live across three railways service right now.
Portals, the Cantonese website and the slide decks.
Nine, nine bags and service seats go perform critical flow approval audit,
market data plus the Hydra X and Canton editors.
Three not service for notification integration and a BFF bet and for front end.
Five roles, aware, protest, issuer, disruptor, investor, ops and admin.
Running on bad demo mode that data.
So you can click around with that or bad info.
Five demos, scripts, modeling the multi-party governance contract,
outs, complete pass key magic link of a real SMTP.
The developer only login removes before public exposure.
One workflow and to end and investors are made a subscription.
Workflow service validated.
Approval service upon the care menu with an SLA timer.
Notification service fan out.
The approval accept the mock Hydra X adapter post the issuance.
The Canton editor commits the them.
The ML script comment and also in memory synchronizer.
Audit locks every state change.
Every transition provable or troubable
replayable and the Canton specific question tokenization stands.
DeFi, composability and the privacy infrastructure setup,
cross-domain data sync.
Each get dedicated that panel and a matching portal rate model.
The Hydra X rail smart is a deliberately things where you are a real API service.
It slots in behind the same interface, not rewrite on the workflow stack.
So this is the business idea.
Hydra position, not just as the regulated rails but also the workflow layer above them for
institutional tokenization in Southeast Asia.
What level per tenant 3 persona is you will disrupt the market operator?
First wage, short duration credit, 30 to 180 day tenant institutional.
That's where the value lies.
Regulator are friendly to the instrument and the cycle is short enough
to prove the platform inside one quarter.
Pricing, hybrid setup plus platform plus volume.
Set up pace for the integration work platform,
pace for the operating interface, volume pace for the rail.
Why this bit letting institution boot their own?
They don't want to maintain workflow code.
Regulators one, one auditable surface to look at and you land adoption per tenant,
rather than per developer.
The unit of growth becomes a desk, not integration and decad.
For open question from the PRD, I bought it on my assumption decision
memo for the each in the repo Q1.
You're else API surface, I bought the mock ready for the drop.
Q2, first product type, short duration credit, FSM,
wired in the workflow service today.
Q3, first tenant, usually led for the fastest land.
Q4, pricing, hybrid setup plus platform plus volume,
non-block shipping the stack.
These three things I want out of this conversation.
One, validate or reject your wedge, short duration credit,
tenant led, wired label, workflow above your list.
Or two, really to check my question one,
two question four, just now.
Three, tell me where my map of Hydra X and 12
roadmap diverge from yours.
Because the gap is where I'm flying blind.
The rest, I yours, not mine.
The workflow layer is moving, grill me on that.