Hey, I mean, I am going to do something ambitious for the next five minutes.
I will tell you what I think your adoption bottleneck on Cantonese.
I will propose a wedge to break it and show you the working code I will around that thesis.
I might be talking past you on a few things, but please, please grill me at the end.
I will find out tonight, then next month.
Here's the thing.
Cantonese wins the regulated multi-party tokenization.
Pricey by design atomic interoperability that model that fits how easy to shine actually work.
Hydra X wins because you are the regulated rails for Southeast Asia.
But the thing is also rails alone don't drive adoption.
The bottleneck between we have rail and issue a ship a product on them is the workflow layer above.
That's where you can grow fastest and that's the layer I would.
Three assumptions are making name up front so you can block them.
One institution won a tenant's surface.
You provide not their own boot.
Two, your roadmap once a white label, workflow plain, not bespoke per deal,
engineering three, Cantonese selective disclosure.
Cantonese selective disclosure is what made that plan defensible.
Again, a generic SaaS competitor tell me which breaks and the rest of this presentation
reshape your answer.
Instead of just pitching, I would that thing the rep.
Instead of just pitching, I would the thing.
The repo is Hydra X at app, live across three railways service right now,
portals, the Cantonese network, home website and the slide decks.
Nine bags and service seats go perform critical flow, approval audit,
market data, plus the Hydra X and Canton editors.
Three, not service for notification, integration and a BFF bet and for
front end. Five rolls, aware, portals, issuer, disruptor, investor, ops and admin,
running on bet demo mode that data.
So you can click around with that or bet end.
Of course, the time is consuming for that.
I just focus on demo.
Five demos, script modeling, the multi-party governance contract,
outs complete, pass key, magic link over real SMTP.
The developer only login removes before public exposure.
One workflow, end-to-end and investors are made a secretion.
Workflow service validated, approval service,
upon the care menu with an SLA timer.
Notification service, fan out, the approval,
keep, accept, demo, Hydra X, adapter, post, their issuance.
The Canton editor commits the damn DML script comment and
also in my mode is synchronized.
Audit locks every state change.
Every transition, approval, approval,
replayable and the Canton specific question, tokenization stands.
DeFi, composability and privacy, infrastructure, setup,
cross-domain, data sync.
Each get dedicated that panel and a matching portal rate model.
The Hydra X rail smart is a deliberately
things where your real API is efficient.
I can of course get into it.
It slots in behind the same interface,
no rewrite on the workflow stack.
If we want to replace it with the real API,
it's almost plot and play.
So this is the business idea.
Hydra position, not just as the regulated rails,
but also the workflow layer above them for institutional tokenization
in Southeast Asia.
What level per tenant 3 persona is your disruptive market operator?
First wage, short duration credit,
3280 day tenant institutional.
That's where the volume lies.
Regulator are friendly to the instrument
and the cycle is short enough to prove the platform inside one quarter.
Pricing, hybrid setup plus platform plus volume.
Set up pace for the integration world platform pace
for the operating interface.
Volume pace for the rail.
Why this bit letting, why this bit letting
institution and build their own,
they don't want to maintain the workflow code.
Regulator one, auditable surface.
Why this bit letting institution build their own?
They don't want to maintain workflow code.
Regulators one, one auditable surface to look at
and you land adoption per tenant,
rather than per developer.
The unit of growth become a desk,
not integration to can.
For open question from the PRD,
I would eat on my assumption decision
memo for the each in the repo.
Q1, yours, API surface, I build the mock ready for the drop.
Q2, first product type, short duration credit,
FSM, wired in the workflow service today.
Q3, first tenant, usually led for the fastest land.
Q4, pricing, hybrid setup plus platform plus volume.
Non-block shipping the stack.
Last one at least.
Three things I want out of this conversation.
One, validate or reject your wedge,
short duration credit, tenant led,
what level workflow above your left.
Or two, really check my question one,
two, question four, just now.
Three, tell me, where am I met of Hydra,
X-Ectual roadmap diverge from yours?
Because the gap is where I'm flying blind.
I don't know what I'm doing right now.
Of course, we limited time of recession.
The rest are yours.
Not mine, the workflow layer is moving.
Gryll me on that.
Thank you very much.